エルさんが
Kimi iro ni Somaru
君色に染まっちゃう
"Dyed With Your Color"
「Music」
「Vocals」
DECO*27
ヲタみん
「Model」
「Choreo」
「Motion」
「Pose」
エルさん
足太ぺんた
つん
ｓｉｖａ、ｃｚ００７５
「MME」
「Stage」
ｒｕｉ、化身バレッタ、
そぼろ、ましまし
落書きさん、公開、
怪獣対若大将P、
ゆづき、＠Ａｉ
「Fonts」
「Camera
& Video」
あんずもじ、ＰｌａｙＤａｙ
ｒｅｍｉｄａｐｙｏｎ
期待してすぐに諦めて
I got my hopes up, just to talk myself down
曖昧な答えに流されては
You're stringing me along with vague answers
自分だけ置いて行かれるような
I feel like I'm being left behind
そんなイメージが胸をつつく夜だ
and that thought pains me at night
覚えてるような　覚えていないような
As I meander through my memories of dreams and aspirations
憧れと記憶を彷徨うよ
I can almost remember, but it's just out of reach
僕は君のために　君は僕のために
Nothing would make me happier than
生まれたならちょっと嬉しいね
If we were born into this world for each other
気付いたら君色に染まってるような
Before I knew it, I was dyed with your color
何気ない言葉で汚して欲しい
I want you to stain me with your casual words
ずっとわからないフリを続けてきたんだ
I've always put up a facade of innocence
この時が来るまで
Anticipating this very moment
もしかして、君と釣り合ってないかな？
Could it be that we weren't meant for each other?
そんな不安もたまに過るけれど
I'd be lying if I said the thought never crossed my mind
いつも困らせてばかりでごめんね
I know I keep getting in your way and I'm sorry, but
ああ、好きだよって伝えたい
All I ever wanted to say was, "I love you"
傷付けないように言葉を探しても
Even if I search for the right words to not hurt you
空回り、気持ちに急かされて
I still end up rushing in with half-complete thoughts
ねぇ間違ってるような これで合ってるような
Why does this feel all wrong, yet so right?
二人の答え、ずっとよろしくね
I'll leave it to you to decide our fates
気付いたら君色に染まってるような
Before I knew it, I was dyed with your color
何気ない言葉で汚して欲しい
I want you to stain me with your casual words
ずっとわからないフリを続けてきたんだ
I've always put up a facade of innocence
この時が来るまで
Anticipating this very moment
もしかして、君と釣り合ってないかな？
Could it be that we weren't meant for each other?
そんな不安もたまに過るけれど
I'd be lying if I said the thought never crossed my mind
いつも困らせてばかりでごめんね
I know I keep getting in your way and I'm sorry, but
ああ、好きだよって伝えたい
All I ever wanted to say was, "I love you"